const insectsQuestions = [
  {
    question: "Where are a cricket’s ears located?",
    answer:
      "On their legs",
  },
  {
    question: "Which butterfly migrates?",
    answer: "Monarchs",
  },
  {
    question: "How much weight can ants lift?",
    answer: "5,000 times their own body weight.",
  },
  {
    question: "What color are elephant hawk-moths?",
    answer: "Pink",
  },
  {
    question: "How are an insect’s eyes different from human eyes?",
    answer: "They are made up of thousands of tiny lenses",
  },
  {
    question: "What’s the largest group of insects?",
    answer: "Beetles",
  },
  {
    question: "How many legs do cockroaches have?",
    answer: "Six",
  },
  {
    question: "Fireflies are also known by what name?",
    answer: "Lightning bug",
  },
  {
    question: "How long does the average housefly live for?",
    answer: "28 days",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the only insect that can turn its head?",
    answer: "Praying mantis",
  },
  {
    question: 'How fast do a bee’s wings beat a second?',
    answer: "190 times a second",
  },
  {
    question: "How long have dragonflies been on Earth?",
    answer: "300 million years",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the loudest insect in the world?",
    answer: "Cicada",
  },
  {
    question: "How fast can Dracula ants move?",
    answer: "90 meters per second",
  },
];
